How do?
So I need you to authorise
the recovery of a vehicle
for me and Gorkem,
and then send another vehicle
to come pick us up.
Really? Why?
What's happened?
So, right...
So you know you said not to
park right next to the flats,
and we weren't going to,
obviously...
But you did.
Well, it was either that
or parking half a mile off
and frogmarching these two
halfway across Sowerby Bridge.
And we wouldn't want you
to wear your little legs out.
So we've... No.
So we've gone in,
we've arrested him,
we're only in there
three minutes, then...
...we've come outside...
I take it we're talking about
the phantom fridge-thrower
again.
It's a microwave this time.
Oh!
- He's diversifying.
- Any available units,
is anyone in the vicinity
- of Baitings Dam?
- Hang on, Shaf.
I'm up that way, Control.
Is that you,
Mrs Cawood?
It is! How's yourself,
Mr Robertshaw?
I'm very fair, thanks,
Mrs Cawood.
Now, I've got a report in
from some...
I think they're, like,
Yorkshire Water people.
- They've found some bones.
- Oh, fair enough.
They've been draining
t'reservoir for maintenance
and a skeleton's popped up,
apparently.
On my way-
Six minutes.
Right, Shaf.
I'll authorise
your recovery vehicle,
but you'll have to sort it out
with Control
about getting picked up.
Or you could speak
to Inspector Taylor
and get him to sort you out.
I'm sure he'll be even more
amused and delighted about it
than I am.
Turned out nice again.
That's it there.
Is it a sheep?
I think
it's an alien life-form.
We get a good few sightings
of 'em round here.
What, sheep?
No, aliens.
9675 to Control.
It's human remains.
Copy that, 9675. We'll get
the on-call SIO down
and send a log across to CSI.
- Catherine.
- Sir.
What do you know?
Torso. Skeleton.
Head, no hands.
Nothing below the waist.
I think he's been there
seven and a half, eight years.
Oh, really? Well, we'll let
the Home Office pathologist
decide that, shall we?
If you like, sir. As you wish.
Heard you're retiring
this year.
Yeah.
Seven months,
one week, three days.
- Teeth intact?
-Mm?
Oh, er, yeah.
And he's got a metal plate
on the right clavicle,
very similar to me own,
except mine's on the left.
What are you doing with
a metal plate, Catherine?
Oh, it's a long story, sir,
from a distant altercation.
His is newer than mine.
Oh, you've decided it's a he,
have you?
What's his favourite sandwich?
Shouldn't think we'll have
too much trouble
identifying him -
her, whoever -
if there's teeth.
You won't have any trouble
at all, sir.
It's Gary Gackowski.
He fell off a third-floor
balcony down at
Upshaw House in Elland
about nine, ten years ago,
when he was off his head
on M-CAT.
Shattered his collarbone.
And I'd recognise those teeth
anywhere.
I nicked him once for a public
order of fence and he bit me.
Went missing
about 18 months later.
That was seven and a half,
eight years since.
People used to say he'd upset
someone he shouldn't have
and been buried in concrete
underpants up at Scammonden,
but happen they were wrong, eh?
This is Baitings.
You might find his legs are
in that blue thing over there.
I'll leave it with you.
Twats.
Tommy, lad,
you've got visitors.
Tommy Lee Royce?
- How do?
- We're from H-Met.
We're arresting you
on suspicion of the murder
of Gary James Gackowski
on or around April 2014.
For the tape,
I'm showing Tommy a photo
of the deceased.
Do you recognise him?
No.
Can you tell me
if you were involved
- in the murder of this man?
- I wasn't.
Can you cast your mind back
eight years
and tell me if you know
or knew of anyone
who was involved in the murder
of this man?
I don't.
Have you ever talked to anyone
about any involvement
you may have had
in the death of this man?
No.
Do you know a lad called
Nazam Miraf?
He's on the same floor as me
at Sheffield.
How would you respond, Tommy,
if I told you
that Naz - Nazam -
has told us that you told him
that you were involved
in the murder of
"that lad they found buried
in concrete
"in that dam up Ripponden"?
Why would I be telling him owt?
What would your reaction be,
Tommy, if I told you
that he told us certain things
that were done to this lad,
to this Gary,
and that he says you told him,
and they were never made known
to the public?
I'd say happen it's him you
need to be chatting to, not me.
Except he was inside
when Gary disappeared.
Well, then he's mixing me up
with somebody else, then.
Either that
or he's making stuff up.
Doing a bit of grassing,
get himself a text
and a few privileges, eh?
This way.
Have you had something to eat?
Yeah, I've had a sandwich
and a wee-wee.
Do you want to sit?
They've made
further disclosures.
And what they're saying now
is that as well as
this Nazam Miraf,
you also told
the prison chaplain
three months ago,
before the body was found,
that you were there when
this Gackowski lad was murdered
and that you helped dispose of
his body in the reservoir.
No comment.
Naz, as you say, might be
hoping for some privileges,
but for this chaplain
to tell us the same tale,
the exact same tale...
That's what's ringing
alarm bells for us, Tommy.
Yeah, well, they're colluding,
aren't they?
Come on, wakey-wakey.
Yes, but why?
Why would they do that?
I don't know. No comment.
Because they don't like me.
I mean, apart from the fact
that, as we've established,
they don't even
know each other.
Hmm?
Naz has never spoken to this
prison chaplain in question,
he's never once met him.
So why would this chaplain,
a bloke who you've told us
is a friend of yours,
a good friend,
why is he coming to us
with almost exactly
the same tale, hmm?
Unless it's true.
Have you ever worn
a St Christopher, Tommy?
A St Christopher.
A necklace with, like,
a St Christopher on it.
- No.
- You have.
Cast your mind back.
Last time you were in prison,
when you went down in 2006,
you were wearing
a St Christopher.
It was logged in your property.
Do you remember?
- Hold up.
- It's OK.
What, 16 years ago?
No, I don't.
It was returned to you
when you left in 2014.
- Can you describe it for me?
- I don't...
- Was it gold or silver or...?
- Er...
Can you tell me
what happened to it?
- No.
- Did you lose it?
- I don't know owt about it.
- But you did have it.
If that's what
you're telling me.
Do you recognise...
- ...this St Christopher?
- That's not
- been disclosed.
- Shut up.
Are you all right, Tommy?
You seem to have become
very interested
when I've shown you
this St Christopher.
Do you recognise it?
No.
How would you react, Tommy,
if I told you that
this St Christopher
was found in the concrete
that was used to weigh down
- Gary Gackowski's body?
- You're lying.
Is it yours, Tommy?
- You planted it.
- No, we didn't.
We know it's yours, Tommy.
This is the log taken
in the prison in 2006.
It describes a silver-coloured
St Christopher pendant
with a V-shaped cut
at five o'clock.
We know you were present,
Tommy,
when Gary Gackowski
went into that concrete.
Gackowski was shot
with a 9mm Glock,
also recovered
from the reservoir.
Ballistics have told us
it's the same weapon
as was used to shoot Ashley
Cowgill two months later,
- in June 2014.
- Oh, aye?
Look, whoever Royce was
working for must have decided
the gun was good for another
job, so they've kept it,
used it to shoot
Ashley Cowgill,
then they've gone back
and dumped it in the reservoir.
And you think this whoever
is Darius Knezevic?
Him and his brother
on a motorbike.
Yeah, before he got too grand
to do his own dirty work
and started getting big ideas
about getting himself elected
onto Bradford City Council.
Look, this has always been
the intel on the ground.
We just haven't been able
to prove it.
I think Royce is this close
to admitting he was present
when Gackowski was shot.
And if he does, we're
optimistic he'll name names.
And if he does, we could have
Darius Knezevic
on a murder charge,
not just for Gary Gackowski,
but for Ashley Cowgill as well.
Finally. At last.
And why do you think
someone like Royce
is going to name names?
We heard Darius Knezevic
ordered Royce's death.
That's how he got his face
cut up like that.
Wasn't meant to just get cut
up, was meant to be dead.
Sorry, ma'am.
Sir, Royce wants to make
a statement.
- Well, that was quick.
- Go on, then.
"I never at any point foresaw
"Gary Gackowski's death.
"I understood that what was
being done was a punishment
"to frighten him. And when
the man pulled out the gun
"and shot him through the head,
"I said,
'What you effing doing?
" 'You said you weren't going
to kill him.'
"I didn't say much else
because I could see
"he was not the sort of person
to argue with.
"I just did what I was told.
"I told him to chuck the gun
in the water, but he refused.
"He said it would be all right
for another job.
"I'm keen to state
"that when I got involved
in this,
"it was on the understanding
"that it was a warning
to the lad.
"I did not know it would end
in his death."
When you say he shot him
through the head,
where exactly?
And when you say "he",
the man who shot him -
have you got a name
for me, Tommy?
Darius Knezevic. Just say it.
It were Chris Oxley.
Chris Oxley? He runs Oldham.
Shit.
What is he doing? Is he blind?
That were a golden opportunity.
Come on!
Tackle him, you twat!
Oh, my God. Move your legs,
you moron!
Anticipate, anticipate!
Where's the defence?!
It's gone in again.
How many's that?
It's 4-0.
Oh, stop it. Poor kid,
he's doing his best.
Tell you what, Cawood -
if you spent as much time
concentrating on
what you're doing, instead of
all this verbal diarrhoea
aimed at everybody else,
you might do better.
No, it's them up there
you want to be going on at.
They don't know what positions
they're in, half of them.
You are skating on
very thin ice.
You little shit stain.
Come on, Ryan, lad! Come on!
What did he say to you,
that Mr Hepworth,
when you chucked t'ba
at him?
- Oh, nothing.
- Didn't look like nothing.
It looked like he upset you.
Yeah, well, revenge is a dish
best sewed cold.
- Who's taught you that?
- Saw it in a film.
And he's a dog. Everyone knows
he's knocking Mrs Oates off.
Is he? Mrs Oates?
There's a joke there somewhere.
And he's a shirt lifting
arse-bandit.
Oi!
Do you want arrested?
Because I can arrest people
for talking like that.
And he can't be like that
if he's knocking off
Mrs Doo-dah.
Unless he's Betty Both-Ways.
- 6-0?
- It's not my fault.
Hey, you're the goalie.
Of course it's your fault.
See, this is
how people think.
He's teasing you.
To be fair,
they were a good side.
I shouldn't even be
in goal.
I should be up front.
Then no—one'd get anywhere near
our goal.
Well, ask him.
Talk to your teacher.
Tell him you want to have a go
- at playing up front.
- He should.
- You should!
- I have!
He doesn't listen.
He's a self-obsessed tosser.
Oi!
And he's knocking Mrs Oates off
when he's not batting for
t'wrong county.
- What have I said?
- That's assault!
- Yeah? Ring the police.
- Oh, here they are.
Sorry I'm late.
You're just in time.
- Where's Ros?
- Oh, she...
She had a headache, so...
Happy birthday, young man!
She sends her apologies.
- You doing anything special?
- Yeah.
- This.
- Daniel and Ann,
they got me a voucher
- to go skydiving.
- Wow.
- It's tomorrow in Sheffield.
- Is he old enough?
I'm 16!
You're all
as mad as each other,
you lot, wanting to do that.
Hey. It's good, that. You have
to use your imagination,
not just sit in front of
a screen,
prodding buttons and shouting.
What are you looking at me
for?
Cos you're as bad as him.
How's the new house?
Oh, we love it.
It needs a lot doing.
Grade
listed.
- You're very lucky.
- Well, they both
work hard, so...
...a
I need now
is some grandchildren
and then we can all relax.
Yeah, I'm doing me best.
Yeah, you know all that means,
though, Clare,
is that it's falling to bits
and you have to do it up like
English Heritage tells you.
She's changing t'subject.
It's gorgeous. It's got, like,
wooden doings and...
- Really? Wooden doings?
- Beams!
Right. Has everyone got
a drink?
Richard, what do you fancy?
Catherine, whose is that thing
outside?
It's mine. I've just bought it.
- What, seriously?
- Mm.
You paid money for it?
- What is it?
- Have you not seen it?
Yeah, I'm going to do it up,
and then I'm going to do
what I've always fancied doing.
I'm going to drive
to the Himalayas.
What have you bought, Mum?
You know most police officers
die within five years of
retirement.
Why?
Because they can't let go.
I don't know.
Cos they've got nothing better
to think about
because the job's made them
all bitter and twisted.
Whereas me,
I'm counting the seconds.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I'm very proud of me 30 years.
I'm the best copper that ever
lived. But Code 1 1 , job done.
I think most of them think
that's it, end of,
but me, I'm just becoming
the person I've always wanted
to be.
Don't take shit off anyone
any more.
I say it like it is.
I know who I am, finally.
And I now know
the be-all and end-all
in't necessarily to get myself
hitched to the first
useless flaky twat of a man
who happens along.
Mm. You've always been
like that.
Yeah, but I'm feeling it now.
Rock on.
What else do you fancy doing?
Zumba? Pilates? Yoga?
- Fuck off.
- Why?
It's dangerous.
Have you never been?
Yoga is dangerous?
Somebody came to do a session
for us
up at t'nick one dinner time.
We were all farting
like billy-o
after the first few moves.
That's not dangerous.
Oh, it is. We gave off
enough methane
to melt a polar icecap.
Greta Thunberg had to come
and speak to us.
We had a flood t'week after,
down Hebden. Do you remember?
Well, that was us lot
cracking off
- up Halifax.
- Who knew?
Oh, it might give you
inner peace,
but there's whole coastal towns
falling into the sea
every time you squeeze yourself
into t'
otus position, so...
...don't you talk to me
about yoga
and then go voting
for the Green Party.
Well, I shall take
my well-intended suggestions
elsewhere.
Yes, kindly do.
Tell you what, though.
What?
It's Ryan's birthday,
and we're just...
---happy. aren't we?
We haven't had one bad word.
We're just having a laugh.
Yeah.
The last few years...
I don't know.
It's all seemed a bit easier
somehow, hasn't it?
We move on, don't we?
In the end.
And he's seemed to
behave himself better
since he moved to Elm Wood.
I think that's been
a big thing.
I wish I knew what that
Mr Hepworth had said to him
when he went up to him
in goal.
He called him
a little shit stain.
You see, this is the thing.
I never know when to tell you
stuff and when not to.
He told me when you were busy
in t'kitchen.
I know. Bastard.
Wants his card marking,
that one.
- Here, look, it's Joe.
- Who the hell's Joe?
- Joe Mamma.
- You twat.
- You're a twat.
- He's a twat.
Who's a twat?
Hepworth.
Oh, yeah. He's a twat.
I dare you to shout,
"Have you had your oats, sir?"
Have you had your oats, sir?
You! Cawood! Get back here.
Fucking hell, he's going to
chase us!
Yeah.
Sorry. Sorry.
Yes?
Hiya. Is that Rob?
It's Leah, Paisley's mum.
It is, yes, hello.
Look, so I don't mind,
and it's really
not a problem. But just so
you know, I've had to pick up
Florence and Poppy again
from school today,
which is fine.
It just means that Paisley's
going to be a few minutes late
for her dance class, which,
honestly, it doesn't matter.
It's just Joanna, I'm just
a little bit worried about her.
It's like the fourth time that
she's rung me last minute,
you know, to ask me
to pick them up and...
Well, look, I really don't want
to say anything out of turn,
but...
...is she drinking?
Rob, are you still there?
- You had a good day?
- Yeah.
- Where's Mummy?
- Bed.
Take your coat off, Poppy.
I, er...
I just had a nap. I'm just
going to go and make tea.
That Leah rang. Said she had to
pick up the girls from school.
Yeah, I just felt a bit
headachey. She didn't mind.
Said it were the fourth...
She did mind.
She asked me
- if you'd been drinking.
- Drinking?
- Are you on something?
- No.
You look like you've taken
something. Have you been to see
- that fucking doctor again?
- No!
I just felt a bit
under the weather so I...
If I find out that
you've been taking
them stupid little pills again,
there's going to be trouble,
because we've had
this conversation.
I haven't been to the doctor.
Well, you look like...
I can see when you've been
taking something.
- Where is it?
- What?
I'm gonna speak to that doctor.
- I haven't been to the doctor.
- So what have you taken?
Nothing!
I just needed a lie down
because I had a headache!
It's more than just a lie down,
innit,
when you can't pick up
your own children from school,
and not for the first time!
Perhaps you don't realise how
obvious it is to other people!
Rob, don't do...
Happy?
I'll go get tea on.
Come here.
Empty your pockets.
No, I'm not emptying
my pockets!
Rob! Get off me!
Rob, get off me! Rob!
Come here.
- No, wait, no, no, no.
- Come here.
- Rob, no.
Rob! Stop!
Stop it!
Rob, no!
No!
Where have these come from?
Hey?
Who gave them to you?
How many have you taken?
- How many have you taken?
- Two!
Well, there's nine missing
from this packet,
so how long have you had 'em?
Do you know, all of us,
all your family,
me, your mum, your dad,
we all thought that
you'd weaned yourself off
this nonsense.
Yes, well, I've been
struggling.
Struggfing?
When?!
And if you're struggling,
you talk to someone.
And where have you got them
from?
Have you got them
on prescription?
No! No.
- They're...
- What, are they knock-off?
You mean they're illegal?
Well, then, perhaps I ought to
ring 999. What do you think?
Think I should do that?
They're not illegal, Rob,
it's diazepam!
They're illegal if you haven't
got a prescription for them.
If you haven't got them
on prescription,
you've got no idea
where they've come from,
or what's in them.
How dare you bring this filth
into my house?
What, are you not thinking?
What if one of the girls
had found them? What if
they'd eaten some of them
thinking they were sweets?
See, this is why you can't be
trusted with anything.
Where?
Where did you get 'em?
Who gave them to you?
Jesus Christ.
You're not even worth fucking.
Right. Well, you might not want
to tell me,
but you'll have to tell
the police.
I'm sure they'll be fascinated
to know all about
- where they've come from.
- Wait, Rob!
Rob, wait!
...which service
do you require?
Police.
Putting you through.
Hold the line.
Rob Hepworth.
And your address, Rob?
22 Holywell Avenue.
Postcode?
HX4 9RK.
Yes, I can.
So, sadly,
what's happened is...
Mr Hepworth?
I recognised his name
on the box when it came up,
so I thought, "Aye-aye,
"I'll have a look at this one
myself."
Didn't recognise me.
Not a flicker.
How many times have I stood
at the side
of that fucking football field
frozen daft?
Anyhow, I didn't say owt.
Where have you been?
I rang over five hours ago.
Been a very busy night, sir.
Yeah, but if you ring 999,
you expect someone to turn up.
You don't expect
to be kept waiting.
We've had a major incident
to deal with in Littleborough,
so I've had to send most
of my team off over the border
to assist our colleagues.
And then, would you believe,
we've had a fatal collision
up Pellon Lane. Two dead.
Now, the operator
you spoke to
ascertained that there was
no-one unconscious,
no-one not breathing, no-one
in need of an ambulance
and no-one's life in danger.
Is that correct?
- Yeah, but...
- So strictly speaking,
that's not a 999 call.
Just FYI, that's a 101 call.
But on the plus side,
you've got a sergeant,
you've got a very experienced
sergeant
to help sort it all out, so...
...do you want to tell me
what's happened?
Where are we going?
Through here?
So I stepped in.
She's sat at the kitchen table.
But do you know
the oddest thing?
Hi, love.
Hi.
You all on a diet?
I could do with a padlock
on my fridge.
Oh, it's just a bit of fun.
Food is fuel.
I'm teaching my little girls
about the importance
of a nutritious
and well-balanced diet.
With a padlock?
And then I notice
he's all Nikes and Adidas,
she's in Primark.
He's built like
a brick shit house
and she's this pasty little
pale thing
with all bruises up her arms.
So this is my wife Jo.
And earlier this evening,
Sergeant...
They've had to send
a sergeant.
When I got in from work,
I found her with what appear
to be prescription drugs.
But whatever they are,
I don't think
she actually got them
with a prescription.
So you rang the police
on your own wife?
What genre of twat does that?
- What's your name, love?
- It's Jo.
-Joanna.
- Are these yours?
Yes.
- These yours, Joanna?
- Yes.
Do you know what they are?
It's diazepam.
Is it, Jo?
Joanna?
Do you have a prescription
for it?
No, she hasn't.
Did you have a prescription
for it, Jo?
Because you need a prescription
if it's diazepam.
I...
I did have a prescription
for diazepam.
No, she didn't.
A few months ago I did.
She had it briefly
on prescription
because she had
a few issues
at one stage, but she dealt
with it very admirably.
And I'm a teacher.
I have my job to think about.
I can't have anything illegal
going on in my private life,
and Joanna knows that.
But these you haven't got on
prescription, is that correct?
- Yeah. No...
- Ask her where she got them.
I found them.
Where did you find them?
Ask her where she found them.
I am sorry, Jo, but I'm going
to have to arrest you.
- Oh, good Lord.
- On suspicion
of possession
of controlled drugs.
Do you understand?
You... You'll have to
give me a few minutes to phone
my mother
to come across from Siddal,
Sergeant.
I've got two little girls
asleep.
- I can't just leave them.
- You don't have to
say anything, all right, love?
But it may harm your defence
if you do not mention
when questioned
something that you
later rely on in court.
All right?
Do you understand that?
Yeah, Mum?
Sorry. Were you in bed?
Yeah.
- Could you pop across?
- Have you got a coat, love?
I'm not going to cuff you.
No-one's here to humiliate you.
Up you get, sweetie.
There's no need to get
your mother out of bed.
Follow on if you like,
but there's really no need.
Hang on, Mum. Sorry. No,
I'll jump in the car with you.
No, you won't.
I'm not a taxi service
and you're not under arrest.
Like I say, you can follow on
if you want, but you'll only
be sat in Reception,
because there'll be nobody
in the interview room
except me and her.
I can get someone to phone you
when she wants picking up,
but it'll be past midnight.
Yeah, now, Mum. Now.
I tried to get her talking
in the car,
but I couldn't get a peep
out of her.
Normally they talk.
Normally when you get 'em away
from a fella like him,
they can't talk fast enough.
But nothing.
So, Joanna, I'm going to
release you on bail.
Does that mean I can go home?
It does.
Is that all right?
Er. . .yeah.
Er...
...thank you.
These will go off
for forensic tests, and...
...depending on what comes
back from the lab,
a decision will be made about
any charges then.
All right?
How long will that take?
About a week or so.
W-Will I go to prison?
No, love.
Not for a first of fence.
I could have let her go with
a caution if she'd given me
a straight tale about where she
got them, but she wouldn't.
She stuck to this fucking
rubbish that she'd found them
on the floor
behind some toilet.
Well, there'll be somebody
she's frightened of.
Oh, yeah.
And then I asked her about
these marks on her arms,
like I didn't know, and
surprise, surprise, it was him.
And then I got
some of the story.
It's depression,
anxiety, panic attacks.
Doctor put her on a short
course of diazepam,
and four months on,
she's hooked,
only he won't prescribe
any more.
And she's got cramps, nausea,
palpitations,
more panic attacks.
I said, "You want to speak
to my sister.
"She runs a group
for people..."
Did you tell her we get
more people turning up
addicted to prescription drugs
than we do heroin?
Yeah.
And I tried to explain to her,
well, very carefully,
what coercive control is
and how not normal it is
to live like that.
And I offered to take her
to the Safeguarding Unit,
but she won't go
because of the girls, which...
Yeah, well.
She's got no money and she
never sees her mum and dad
because he don't like 'em.
And same with her friends -
well, she has none any more.
I just said, "Let me help you.
He's isolated you,
"he's infantilised you."
But you know, you can only
lead a horse to water.
She says, "
'
have to go.
"He'll be waiting for me
in Reception,"
which, lo and behold, he was.
Creepy to think he teaches
our Ryan, though, eh?
Oh, yeah. Well, next time
I'm stood at the side
of that football field,
I'll make myself known to him.
That'll shock him.
Right. OK.
You just wait for me there.
That's it.
Get yourself in there, love.
That's it, love. Pop your hand
through there. That's it.
Lunch boxes.
That's yours, in't it, love?
Start again.
What you saying?
Last night, right,
at that house down there,
a police car showed up, right?
And about 20 minutes later,
the woman got put
in the back of it.
Which house?
That one, with the red Audi.
Which woman?
That one with
them two little girls.
- When was this?
- Last night.
- Yeah - what time?
- I don't know.
Ten, 11, half 11 ish.
And she got put in the back
of a police car?
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Has she murdered him?
Like arrested?
" Dad!
_
You're sat on my homework!
- I feel sorry for them kids.
- Oh, sorry.
Those kids.
The littlest one,
that Poppy one?
She never takes her coat off.
Mum!
Dad squashed my chemistry
with his skinny fat bottom,
and I spent nearly half an hour
doing that last night.
So are you saying...?
She got put in the back of
a police car.
- Hiya.
- I've only got ten minutes.
I heard Haniya this...
...morning saying she saw you
go off in a police car
last night.
Yeah. It was him. He rang 999.
Why?
He found some of the pills
that you're giving me.
- How?
- Well, just...
So where are they now?
He gave them to the police.
Are you kidding me?!
They'll not be able to trace it
back to you, will they?
Did you get rid of
all the packaging?
- Yeah.
- All of it?
- Are you...
Are you sure? This is serious!
I'm sure.
- So what did they take?
- Just the pills.
In what? In...
Little bag, a little bag
- that I had.
- This is important, Joanna.
That's how they trace stuff.
I'm not stupid.
What a pig, ringing the police.
You're his wife!
I've kept telling you.
So what did you tell them
about where you got 'em?
I just said that I found them
on the floor behind a toilet
in a pub.
- Did they believe you?
- I don't know.
She wrote it down,
the policewoman did,
and she seemed more interested
in what a bastard he was
- than anything else.
- So, so...
...what did they charge you
with?
Nothing yet. They have to wait
for the pills to come back
from being, I don't know,
analysed.
They won't be able to
trace it back to you
like that, will they?
Not without the packaging.
And you definitely took them
out the little blister packs
as well as the boxes?
Yeah.
Right. I better go.
Can you...
Can you get me some more?
I'll pop them out for you.
Have you got something
to put them in?
Do you, erm...
Do you want to go to bed?
No, you're all right.
I've got to get to work.
Right.
Mr Brooks is here for
his prescription, Mr Bhatti.
Do you want to come through,
Ezra?
There you go.
1,200 quid.
You do always get rid of
all the packaging properly,
don't you?
Before you give it to people.
Do you think I'm thick?
No, I just...
You having a bad day?
No.
I've got three more people
interested. Clientele.
I could do another, oh,
120 jellies next week.
I think moderation
is the thing.
All right?
You're a Good Samaritan,
Mr Bhatti.
You make the world
a better place.
Mm.
This is the way.
OK.
- Morning, love.
- You all right?
- Grappo
o's.
- No.
- Yeah, I'll book it.
- Don't!
-
'
book Abba.
- OK.
- Oh, seriously?
- Yeah, book who you like.
I'll be at home
having a cup of tea.
Oh, for God's sake,
what's up with you?
Well, you didn't have
a retirement do!
I haven't retired!
From being a copper, you did.
I think we had
a little drinks do.
But I'm not popular
like you are.
I'm not popular.
You are!
In certain circles you are.
They'd probably all
just turn up to take a pop
and say good... What do you
mean, in certain circles?
You are popular
in certain circles.
Well, in what circles
am I not popular?
I don't know. You tell me.
You're the one saying
you're not popular.
Yeah, but who were you
thinking of when...?
- Nobody.
- When you said it?
- Nobody!
- Well, who was on your mind?
Well, there's a few top brass
you've pissed off
over the years, aren't there?
There was that time
that you told Mike Taylor
to shove his pips up his arse.
Think that might have been
a game-changer.
Anyway, you're very popular
with...
...the troops, the gang,
the rank and file, aren't you?
When you're not upsetting them.
I've just done my job.
I've toughened them up.
I'm sorry if that makes me
unpopular.
You didn't have
- a little drinks do.
- I did!
Well, I don't remember
coming.
Were you sulking?
It's either that
or you didn't invite me.
Why would I not invite you?
Of course I invited you.
I don't think you did, Joyce.
Oh...
Just forget it.
OK.
It's a wonder you have
any friends at all.
Well, I don't,
according to you.
According to you,
I'm Billy fucking No-Mates.
God, you're hard work.
- Catherine?
- Mike!
- Got a minute?
- Not really, but seeing as
it's you and given that I need
all the friends I can get...
- Oh, for fuck's...
- All right, Joyce?
I never know whether she's
joking or just being a pillock.
Have you booked Grappo
o's?
No, I haven't.
Do you want me to?
Well, if you've got the stamina
and the determination,
you knock yourself out, chuck.
Sit down.
I've had a phone call.
Might be nothing.
Are you going to give me
some clues?
Samantha Greenwood.
Do you know her?
She's the prison liaison
officer at Dewsbury.
Do I? I don't know. Probably.
She was at this conference
in Reading last week,
week before,
with a lot of other PLOs.
And apparently someone said
to her that someone else
had said to them that
that Catherine Cawood
must be getting soft,
letting her grandson
go visiting Tommy Lee Royce.
What?
So hang on.
Someone else said to
someone else who said to her,
- this Samantha...
- There's her number
if you want to ring her.
...that they'd seen Ryan?
No, I don't think
they could have.
I think they must have talked
to a prison officer
during a visit to the prison,
who must have said he or she,
this prison officer,
had seen Ryan visiting Tommy.
So it's fourth-hand
information.
It's Chinese whispers,
it's bollocks.
That's why I didn't know
whether to say anything
or not. Anyway,
- you've got her number.
- I think somebody has got
their wires crossed.
How would they know our Ryan,
for starters?
Anyway, how would he get there?
He's just gone 16 and he's
really not that well organised.
He's only just nicely got
a train to Leeds on his own,
well, with Cesco,
and that was a palaver.
How the hell would he
get to Gravesend and back
on his own without me knowing?
He in't in Gravesend.
Royce.
He got transferred
to Sheffield.
When?
18 months, two years ago.
Didn't you know?
Why would I, Mike?
I thought there were
a court order in place
to stop him having any contact
with either you or Ryan.
So it doesn't matter
where he is.
Yeah, there was,
and I renewed it.
I mean, it might have lapsed
again by now because, I mean,
it's been, God, how long?
Seven years?
But that's because I didn't
think I needed to renew it.
He never mentions him,
thank God.
He never even thinks about him.
I can't remember the last time
he mentioned him.
I think she's just...
Whatever she's heard,
I think she's just...wrong.
Can you ask him?
No, no, no.
No, I'm not doing that.
- She say owt else?
- No.
I don't... Oh, only that he was
with a man and a woman.
A man and a woman?
He'd have to be.
Any kid would have to be
if they're under 18.
What man?
And what woman?
They'll have a record of
his visiting orders
- at the prison, Mike.
- They will.
I'll find out who the governor
is and drop him an email.
Don't hold your breath.
Prison Service are
worse staffed than we are.
Can't be that far off
Royce's court date
for that Gary Gackowski murder,
can it?
Next week. Right. Off you pop.
Look busy.
I'll give you a shout
if I hear owt.
And don't worry about it,
Catherine.
Like you say,
it'll be Chinese whispers.
Buenos dias.
Mi coche esté danado.
Perdén,
no lo entiendo.
Podria repetirlo, por favor?
Perdén, no lo entiendo.
Podflas repefiflo, pot favor'?
Dénde esté el taller mecénico
més cercano?
So I went straight back
to our house
and went into his bedroom.
I didn't find anything.
Well, what did you expect
to find?
Letter?
Visiting order?
I think...
...it's unlikely, Catherine.
Yeah, I know.
But suddenly Royce
is in Sheffield,
which I never knew,
and there's this man and
this woman taking him there,
or taking someone there.
Happen he's got other kids,
I don't know, but I'm still
left thinking things.
Wouldn't be Daniel and Ann
because she won't go anywhere
near him any more than I would.
It's not you and Ros.
Definitely not me and Ros.
Clare and Neil have taken him
to watch football matches
when I've been working, but...
See, Neil,
I don't know about Neil.
I've never been sure
about Neil,
but Clare, she just wouldn't.
She wouldn't do that to me,
would she?
- No. No.
- No.
I don't... No.
So then I'm thinking, well,
maybe Cesco's mum
and some fella that she knows,
but then why the hell
would they?
Or some teacher, but then...
...why? And the ethics,
they just...
...wouldn't,
and I don't know anybody else.
There's Nev.
Nev takes him to see
Man City play now and again
- but Nev would never...
- Never in a million years
would Nev do that.
Any more than Ann would.
Yeah, so I don't know.
Don't know.
- What's going on with Ros?
- Oh...
She's sleeping in
the spare room.
I'm sorry.
Mm.
Nev's asked me out
for a meal.
Nev?
Rang me after
Ryan's birthday tea.
You're not jealous, are you?
I mean...
...you know, good luck.
He's old enough
to be your grandad, but...
Hardly.
How old do you reckon he is?
70?
Easily.
75?
76, 77?
Does Ann know?
- Does Daniel?
- It wouldn't be illegal.
No. Just...
What?
"Tell me, Catherine,
what first attracted you
"to the millionaire
- "Nevison Gallagher?"
- Fuck off.
See, you're smiling.
Ask him.
Ask Ryan straight out
about this other business.
No.
Why?
Because I don't want
to put ideas in his head
that he can visit him
if they're not there already.
After you, love.
Can I help?
Er, me cousin, he needs to
see the pharmacist about, er...
Personal.
Mr Bhatti?
Yeah?
This man's cousin needs...
His English ain't great.
But he's been with this lass
and he thinks
he's picked summat up.
It's a bit swollen
and there's, like, discharge.
But he's not registered
with t'surgery, so...
OK. Er...
Do you want to just
come through here?
This way. Come on.
You go on, love. I'm just
waiting for me cousin.
Sit down.
I can give you something
to ease the symptoms, but...
Whoa!
I've heard you've started
helping people, Faisal.
Which is fine.
Only trouble is, we run
these postcodes round here,
- not you. Do you understand?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
I was starting to think
I'd bitten off more than
I could chew, anyway.
Yeah, but...
Good, but the thing is,
we still need you to keep on
doing what you're doing.
So when you collect
your winnings,
you'll be handing them over
to us, OK?
No, I won't. I can't.
- I can't.
- You will.
I can't do it any more because
the police might be onto me.
Well, till we know
one way or the other,
we'll stick with the
arrangement, do you understand?
We know you're turning over
- upwards of 1,800 quid a week.
- No!
Yeah, you are.
So don't short-change me.
It's not that much!
It's only ever about 1,000
- at the most.
- Well, why don't you
make up the difference, then?
You can do a bit more
easy enough.
I've told you, the police
might be onto me.
Don't worry about t'po
ice.
What do you mean?
I mean it's me you need to
worry about now.
We know where your Maira
and your little...little Haniya
go to school.
Been watching 'em.
We know what time they leave,
we know what bus they get on.
We know whose houses they go to
at dinner times when they're
- meant to be in school.
- Who's we?
Eh, we probably know more about
what they get up to
than you do.
Listen, Faisal.
Nobody wants to see 'em
get hurt, hmm?
Nobody wants to see anybody
get abducted
and treated like bitches.
Yeah?
I don't.
So don't you worry about
t'po
ice. All right?
We'll worry about the police.
Yeah?
We'll see you
in a couple of days.
No! That's...
Oh, is that not convenient?
Mm? Mm?
It's convenient for me.
Better go get me
a little box of
whatever it is
you're going to give me.
Don't want your little girl out
there thinking things, do we?
He's to come back
and see you again
in a couple of days, yeah?
Nice one.
I rang the MHRA
to see if anyone
knew anything about
the illegal supply of diazepam
in and around Elland.
Their PLO's just rung me back
and said, "Yeah, we're aware
"there's a problem and there is
an ongoing inquiry."
- Knezevics?
- No doubt.
Yeah, the ever-lovely
Knezevics.
The Teflon-coated Knezevics.
I should have said, "Right,
you take your time, love,
"we'll just mop up as usual."
What?
I've got some intel for you
from the prison in Sheffield.
You're not going to like it.